（カブト）おかしなものだね。
（サスケ）何がだ？
It's so funny...
（カブト）今　こうして見ると
ずいぶん仲がよく見える。
What is?
Right now, you two look like
あれだけ憎んで　派手な兄弟ゲンカを
してたはずなのにね。
you're quite friendly
with each other.
What happened to those brothers
who fought and hated each other?
((あんたが　その眼を
いくら使おうが→
No matter how much you use
those eyes of yours...
(この俺の憎しみで
幻は現実になる))
I'll use my hatred...
to turn fantasy into reality!
キミが　イタチを倒すときに→
It's not hard to guess that something
happened between you two,
何かあっただろうことは
うかがえるが→
back when you took him down...
一度　死んだ人間に
今更　何を聞きたいっての？
But what is it that you want to ask
of a once-dead man?
真実だ。
The truth.
あれれ？　もしかしてだけど…。
Oh really?
Could it be?
With the way you're talking...
あ…　いや　その言い方→
疑ってるみたいに
聞こえるね…　イタチを。
you don't really trust
Itachi, after all?
サスケ君。
Sasuke...
キミ　すでに　イタチの真実を
知ってるってことか？
Maybe you already know
the truth about Itachi?
どうりで　イタチを倒したあと
キミは　木ノ葉の里に帰らず→
No wonder you didn't return
to the Leaf
after defeating Itachi.
That's why you joined the Akatsuki
who plotted the Leaf's destruction!
逆に里を狙う　暁に入るわけだ。
フン…　なるほど。
I see now...
It all makes so much sense
to me now.
なら　いろいろと
今のキミの行動にも合点がいく。
That's why you intend to
destroy the village
だからこそ　キミは→
兄を苦しめた木ノ葉を
潰す気でいるんだね？
that caused your brother
so much pain.
As expected.
You're not denying it.
やっぱり否定はしないね。
So you followed your brother,
who you happened across,
とにかく　偶然会った兄に→
all the way here to find out
the truth once and for all.
真実を直接
確かめようと　ここまで来た。
Like "Is this what happened then?"
and "What about that time?"
あのときは
ああだったのか？　とか→
このときは
こうだったのか？　と細かくね。
in complete detail...
Like I said,
your brother is a liar!
さっきも言ったけど→
まあまあウソつきだからねぇ
キミの兄さんは。
I know.
So isn't it odd?
わかるよ。　なら…　おかしいよね？
Itachi was willing to kill
his own family
イタチは同胞を殺してでも
木ノ葉を守ろうとした男だよ。
to protect the village.
Isn't that the opposite of
what you're trying to do?
キミのやろうとしていることと
敵対してないかい？
Well...
I'm the one who wants
what you want, Sasuke!
いや…　むしろ僕のほうが→
キミと同じ目的を
持ってるんだよ　サスケ君。
After all, Lord Orochimaru could not
complete Leaf Destruction.
大蛇丸様が夢半ばで終わった→
And it is I who inherited that task.
木ノ葉崩しを
継ぐ者でもあるからね。
So think carefully...
Now's the time to stab Itachi
in the back and join me.
さあ　よく考えて。
イタチを後ろから突き刺し
こっちへ来るなら今だよ。
What? You don't have to feel guilty.
なに　罪悪感を
感じることはないよ。
He's already dead.
He's just an imitation.
そいつは本当は死んでる。
It was a mission.
ただの模造品だから。
To be the sole perpetrator of
his clan's slaughter and
((マダラ：任務だった。
一族を殺した犯罪者として→
become a Rogue Ninja with
his reputation in tatters.
All of that was his mission.
汚名を背負ったまま
抜け忍となること…。
And Itachi completely
fulfilled his duty...
そのすべてが任務だった。
With one exception...
そして　イタチは
その任務をまっとうした。
He could not bring himself...
to kill his younger brother.
ただ一点の失敗を除いてはな。
(弟だけは…　殺せなかった…))
for some reason the moon is one size larger tonight
konya no tsuki wa nazeka hitomawari ookikute
it's shining brighter than it usually does
itsumo yori akaruku terasu
I trudge along the road home with my shoulders hunched
senaka wo marumete tobotobo kaeru michi
at any time I will always have a friend
donna toki mo mikata wa iru
without saying a word, it's all right to cry
nani mo iwazu naketara ii ne
once my tears dry, it will all be over
namida ga karetara owari
I need to become stronger...
motto boku ga tsuyoku naranakya
sorrow is the first step towards independence
kanashimi wa jiritsu he no ippo
how many times do I have to get hurt to forget the pain?
nando kizutsukeba itami wo wasureru
when I bleed red, I'm reminded of life
akai chi wo nagaseba inochi wo omoidasu sa
I collapse on the road with my arms and legs spread out
michi ni taore dainoji ni
I look up at the sky and think
sora wo miagete omou
true loneliness is someone without a past
shin no kodoku to wa kako no nai mono
someone who only knows the present
ima shika shiranu mono
((暁の　うちはイタチが
死んだという情報が入った。
To Each Their Own Leaf
お前らのビンゴブックにも
対象外の印をつけ　外しておけ。
We received intel that
Itachi Uchiha of the Akatsuki is dead.
裏切り者も　ついに死んだか。
Put a mark on his image and
remove him from your Bingo Book.
So that traitor is dead at last.
しかし　あのイタチを　いったい
誰がやったんです？　隊長。
弟の　うちはサスケだそうだ。
But Captain,
who was able to kill him?
同胞殺しが同胞に殺されるとは
皮肉なもんだ。
Looks like it was
his kid brother, Sasuke.
罰ですよ。　それだけの
悪行をやったんすからね。
How ironic...
His own brother killed the one
who slaughtered his family.
あげく　暁にまで入って
木ノ葉を襲う始末。
Serves him right!
After the atrocious thing he did!
あいつは木ノ葉の歴史上
まれに見る大悪人ですよ。
Not only that, he joined up
with the Akatsuki
and came after the Leaf Village!
こいつだけは
俺たちの手で倒したかったぜ。
He's the most notorious villain
in Hidden Leaf history!
Damn it, I wish we got
our hands on him first!
イタチほどの特Ｓ級犯罪者をやった
弟には→
国と里からの勲章と
多額恩給が出るよな。
Since he took down such
a special S-Class criminal,
his little brother will probably
receive many decorations
いったいいくらかな？
and a large bounty from
the nation and village, right?
カネの問題じゃない。　不謹慎だぞ。
I wonder how much?
あ　まあ…　そうですけど。
It's not a question of money.
You're out of line.
（マダラ）やつらは真実を知らん。
Well... I know, but...
それに　ここでは人が多すぎる。
They don't know the truth...
俺が真実を語る！
Besides, there are
too many people around.
やめておけ。　こいつらが
イタチの真実を上に確かめようが→
I'll teach them the truth!
Don't...
木ノ葉上層部は
必ず　それを否定する。
Even if they try to confirm the truth
about Itachi with their superiors,
the Leaf's elders will
deny it vehemently.
今の火影でさえ
それは知るところではない。
Even the current Hokage
doesn't know the facts.
それに　イタチは事実
うちはを皆殺しにし→
Furthermore...
Itachi did slaughter the Uchiha,
and he joined the Akatsuki
一度　暁として
木ノ葉を襲うフリをした。
誰も真実は信じまい。
on the pretense of attacking
the Hidden Leaf.
No one will believe the truth...
現に　お前でさえなかなか…。
Look how long it took you.
こんなやつらのために…。
For bastards like them...
裏切り者の烙印を押すような
やつらのために　兄さんは…。
For these bastards
who easily brand him a traitor...
イタチの望んだ結果だ。
my brother...
This is exactly what
Itachi wanted.
(それが嫌なら
お前は何を望む？))
If you don't like it,
what is it that you want?
一緒にするな。
We're not the same.
俺の木ノ葉崩しは
俺だけのものだ。
My Leaf Destruction is mine alone!
イタチの生き様は
僕も　よく理解できる。
I understand very well
why Itachi chose that life.
僕も　イタチと同じさ。
I was just like him...
木ノ葉の忍に
拾われたはいいが→
It was nice being found
by a Leaf Shinobi,
出生のわからない僕は
すぐにスパイとして育てられ→
but because my background
was a mystery,
I was raised to be a spy.
敵に信用されるようにと
医療忍術を叩き込まれた。
In order to become someone
who could be trusted,
Medical Ninjutsu was
drilled into me.
ずっと他里を
あちこちスパイして回った。
I went from village to
village spying...
偽りの自分を演じ
ずっとウソをつきとおし→
I pretended to be someone else,
living a life of lies.
With no place for the real me.
本当の自分の居場所すらない。
I had no friends
who knew the real me.
本当の自分を知る仲間もなく
自分を消す作業が続く。
I continued to work
on suppressing myself.
And around the time I stopped knowing
who I even was anymore...
そして己が
何者かわからなくなった頃→
the Hidden Leaf Village
stopped trusting me
木ノ葉の里は
僕を信用できなくなり→
and I was relieved of my mission.
任務から降ろした。
Both Itachi and I worked for
the good of the Leaf Village,
イタチも僕も
木ノ葉の里のために働いたのに→
but in return, all we got
was dishonor and disgrace!
見返りは　ただの汚名と不名誉だ。
What in the world has
the Leaf Village ever done for us?
木ノ葉の里が　僕らに→
いったい何をしてくれた
っていうんだい？
How Itachi lived is what led to
the creation of the current you.
イタチの生き様があって
生き残りの　今のキミが形成された。
And though I am still alive,
僕は　まだ死んでないだけで
キミと同じものが形成された。
something similar to you
was born from me too.
No one understands you
better than I.
僕以上に　キミを理解できている者は
他にいない。
Thus, I will be your big brother
and stick by your side.
だから今度は
僕が兄として　キミのそばにいよう。
Now... join me...
さあ　一緒に。
Don't listen to him, Sasuke.
（イタチ）サスケ。　耳をかすな。
He was an even better spy
than I was.
やつは　俺以上のスパイだった。
Which means, he's even better
than me at lying.
つまり　俺以上に
ウソがうまいってことだ。
And...
No matter what darkness or
contradictions lie within the village,
それにな　里がどんなに
闇や矛盾を抱えていようと→
I am still Itachi Uchiha of the Leaf!
俺は　木ノ葉の　うちはイタチだ。
Sasuke... It's my fault
you're like this right now.
サスケ。
お前をそうしてしまったのは
他でもない俺だ。
I know I have no right
to advise you in any way.
今更　お前の決断に→
But I hope you'll hear me out
どうこう言える立場では
ないのかもしれない。
because I have to
tell you something.
だが　こうなってしまった以上
ひと言だけ→
ちゃんと言っておきたい
言葉がある。
But first, let's take care
of business...
and stop this guy.
ちゃんと場を整えてからな。
だから　まずは
やつを止めるぞ。
You cannot kill me
as long as I am the user
of the Reanimation Jutsu.
僕が　穢土転生の術者である以上→
And I can instantly recover
from any injury you inflict.
僕は殺せない。
It's meaningless.
手傷を負わせても
この体の回復力があるかぎり→
I shut down my eyesight.
それも　意味をなさない。
So the much-touted genjutsu
of your Visual Prowess
僕は　視力を断った…。
won't work on me...
You brothers can't beat me!
キミら自慢の瞳力の幻術も
一切　効かない。
Because I cast it,
キミたち兄弟に　勝ち目はないよ。
this Reanimation Jutsu
is invincible!
この僕だからこそ
この穢土転生の術が無敵なのさ！
It's a pain listening to him.
But he explained
the situation perfectly.
やつの演説は　聞くに耐えんが…。
I don't need you to tell me that.
So... what should we do?
状況説明だけは　一理ある。
He doesn't know the true power
of the Uchiha.
言われなくても　わかってる…。
で…　どうする？
The Uchiha have a Visual Jutsu
that can be used
やつは
うちはの本当の力を知らない。
on an opponent without eyesight...
In exchange for losing the light
in one's eyes.
うちはには→
相手の視覚に訴えることなく
はめる瞳術がある。
光を失うことと引き換えにな。
イザナギ…？
イザナギを知ってるのか？
Izanagi...?
You know about Izanagi?
ダンゾウと戦ったとき
それを使ってきた。
Danzo used it when I fought him.
お前…　よく生きていたな。
You're lucky to be alive.
それはいい。
どうやって　イザナギを使う？
Never mind about that...
How do we use Izanagi?
イザナギではない。
I'm not talking about Izanagi.
それと対になる　もう１つの禁術。
Another Forbidden Jutsu that
is considered its other half.
もう１つ！？
Another?!
すでに　仕込みは整った…。
I've already laid the plan.
やつの運命を握る　究極の瞳術…。
An Ultimate Visual Jutsu that
holds his fate within its grasp.
イザナミだ！
Izanami!
《イザナミ！？》
Izanami?!
イザナギが　運命を変える術なら→
If Izanagi is a jutsu
that changes one's fate,
イザナミは　運命を決める術！
then Izanami is a jutsu
that decides it!
サスケ…　俺から離れるな。
Sasuke... Do not leave my side.
《運命を決める術！？
イザナギと同じような術が　他にも…》
A jutsu that decides one's fate?
So there's another jutsu
similar to Izanagi?!
何をしようとしているのか
知らないけど→
I don't know what you're up to...
今の僕には　何も通じないよ…。
but nothing will work against me.
僕が何者なのか→
It seems you still don't
understand just who I am!
キミたちは
わかっていないようだね！
仙法　無機転生！
Sage Art...
Inorganic Animation!
イタチ！
Itachi!
生体機能を持たないもの自体に→
This jutsu brings
the lifeless to life
生命を与え　コントロールする術さ…。
and allows me to control them.
チャクラで操る術とは　わけが違うよ。
It's different from a jutsu that
simply manipulates with chakra...
いきすぎてるだろ？
A bit extreme, don't you think?
スサノオで　サスケ君を守った分
遅れたね…。
Protecting Sasuke with
your Susano'o slowed you down.
なに…
サスケ君は　傷つけやしないよ。
Well, don't worry.
I would never harm Sasuke.
僕の大切な実験体だから…。
He's my precious test subject.
さて…　これで　また
頭の中を上書きする。
Now then...
Time to rewrite your mind with this.
どうなるかは　わかるだろ。
You know what will happen, right?
天照！
Amaterasu!
最大の攻撃瞳術は→
最大の防御にもなるってことだね。
So... The Ultimate Visual Jutsu
offensive attack
熱くて鍾乳洞も
もとに戻っちゃったか。
is also the Ultimate Defense...
It's so hot, the limestone cave
went back to being just a cave.
すまない…　サスケ…。
悪いが　僕の勝ちだ。
I'm sorry... Sasuke...
すべてを成し　制することに
近づきつつある僕にとって→
Sorry, but this is my win.
I am so near the point
どうしても　失敗する姿が
思い浮かばないんだよ。
where I can achieve and
control everything...
かつて　大蛇丸様が集め
研究し尽くしてきた→
I can't imagine myself failing.
自然界の法則や原理が→
All the laws and principles
of nature,
which Lord Orochimaru researched
and compiled for so long...
いまや　僕の中に
すべて　蓄積されている。
are now stored and
being used inside of me.
人から蛇へ　蛇から龍へ…。
そして　この世で　いちばん
六道仙人に近しいのは　この僕…。
I have evolved from human
to snake to dragon.
I am the closest thing
in this world
それに比べれば
うちはの名など…。
to the Sage of Six Paths.
言ってろ！
お前に　うちはの何がわかる！
Compared to me, the Uchiha are...
Shut up!
いいか！
What would you know...
about the Uchiha?!
Listen...!
（イタチ）カブト　お前を見ていると→
Kabuto...
まるで　かつての
俺を見ているようだ。
When I look at you,
it's like looking at my former self.
だからこそ…　お前は負ける。
And that is why you will lose...
いいかい　僕は　もう脇にはいない。
Listen... I'm not on
the sidelines anymore.
今は　この戦争の中心と
言ってもいい。
You could say I'm a central figure
in this war!
暁を手玉にとり
戦争を有利に操り→
I had the Akatsuki twisted
around my little finger,
うちはの兄弟をも
追い込んでる。
and manipulated this war
to my advantage...
and I even pushed
the Uchiha brothers into a corner.
（イタチ）俺にとって　お前は→
I hate you,
but I understand you.
対立と共感
２つの感情を抱かせる。
お前も俺と同じ　スパイとして→
We were both spies
偽りの世界を
歩いてきたものだからな。
who lived false lives
in this world.
俺も　己が何者か
わかってなかった。
I didn't know who I really was
at one point either.
自分を知るということは→
I finally understand that
to know oneself
すべてを成し　完璧になることでは
ないと　今　やっとわかる。
is not to achieve everything
and become perfect.
それは　己に何ができ
何ができないかを知ることだ。
It's knowing what you can
and cannot do.
負け犬らしい方便だね。
Sounds like the words of a loser.
できないことを認めろと…。
Acknowledging what
you cannot do...
諦めろってことかい？
Isn't that the same as giving up?
違う。　己ができないことを→
No.
It is to be able to forgive oneself
許すことができるように
なることだ。
for the things one cannot
do by themselves.
すべてができないからこそ
それを補ってくれる仲間がいる。
You can't do everything yourself.
That's why you have comrades
who can help you.
And it also makes sure that
本来　できたであろうことを
ないがしろにしないためにもな。
you don't miss the things
that you can still accomplish.
自分が何者か知りたければ→
If you want to know
who you are...
You must reexamine and
acknowledge your true self.
本当の自分を見つめなおし
認めることだ。
I failed to do that.
俺は　それに失敗した。
I lied to everyone and I lied to myself...
and I deluded myself.
皆にウソをつき　己自身にも
ウソをついて　ごまかしてきた。
Those who cannot acknowledge
themselves will fail...
己自身を認めてやることが
できないやつは失敗する。
Just like I did.
かつての俺のようにな。
And what would you two
really know about me?
キミらこそ　僕の何を知ってる？
I have been pursuing who
and what I am in my own way.
僕は　僕のやり方で　ずっと
自分が何者なのかを探してきた。
My whole life...
ずっと。
((あの町の子だろ？
I bet he's from that city...
この前　戦闘のあったとこだよ。
Where that recent battle was!
（ウルシ）どうする？　姉ちゃん。
What'll we do, Sis?
こいつ　頭から　血　出てるし→
He's bleeding from the head.
もうじき死ぬぜ。　連れてくの？
He's gonna die soon.
（ノノウ）ウルシ　あなたのときよりは
軽傷です。
Are you gonna take him?
Urushi...
His injuries are less severe
than yours were.
（ノノウ）心配しないで。
Don't worry.
こう見えても
医療忍術が　少しできるの。
I may not look it,
but I know some Medical Ninjutsu.
ご両親は？
Where are your parents?
お名前は　何ていうの？
What's your name?
なんもわかんねえのかよ！
ったく！
Man... Don't you understand anything?!
ウルシ　肩を…。
Urushi, lend him your shoulder.
You're lucky, kid!
(てめえ　運がよかったな！
ほら　俺の肩につかまれ！))
Come on, grab my shoulder!
That's my first memory...
（カブト）それが最初の記憶。
I was a nobody
最初から　僕は何者でもなかった。
and had nothing from
the very beginning.
僕には　何もなかった。
I didn't know my parents...
親を知らず
自分の名すら知らない。
I didn't even know my name.
Your wound seems
to be healing nicely.
((傷の具合は　いいみたいですね。
Hey, at least say, "thank you"!
てめえ　ありがとうくらい言えよ！
礼儀も知らねえのか？
Don't you have any manners?!
Hey, we don't want anything
to happen to you again,
おい　また何かあるといけねえから
これでも被ってな！
so put this on!
Ow...
イテ！
礼儀どころか親も知らねえし→
You don't have manners,
you don't have parents...
you don't even know your name.
That's a first for me!
自分の名前まで知らねえやつは
初めてだよ。
あなたは
今日から　ここで暮らすのよ。
You'll be living here
with us now.
つまり　今日から私が
あなたのお母さんです。
In other words, I am your mother,
starting now.
何かあったら
遠慮はいりませんよ。
You can always ask me
for whatever you need.
でも　こいつ
名前もねえってのは不便だよな。
It's inconvenient that
he doesn't have a name...
（ノノウ）そうね。
You're right...
何がいいかしら？
What would be a good name?
カブトってのは　どうかしら？
How about...
"Kabuto" like the helmet?
雑。
適当。
– Sounds simple.
– That was quick.
You called it by just how he looks.
見たまんまじゃん。
It's best not to overthink things.
考えすぎないことが
いちばんです。
– I'll think of something.
– Not you!
俺が考えるよ。
What would be a good name?
何がいいと思う？
Hey, he smiled!
（ウルシ）こいつ今　笑った。
I think he likes that name!
結構　気に入ったみたいだぜ
この名前。
（ノノウ）よかった。
Oh good...
((ウルシ：てめえ
ありがとうくらい言えよ。
(礼儀も知らねえのか？))
At least say, "thank you"!
Don't you have any manners?!
う～ん　どうしたものか。
国や里からの補助金だけでは
もう　やっていけませんよ。
Hmm... What to do...?
We can't get by with
just subsistence aid
国と里に　もう少し→
from the village or nation anymore.
かけあってみるしか
ありませんね。
We have to talk to them once more!
もう　一文たりとも
出しちゃくれませんよ。
しかし　運営はギリギリです。
Neither the village nor
the nation will give us a cent more.
But we're barely scraping by.
また一人　増えたばかりですし。
And we just took another one in...
わかりました。
私が　なんとかします。
I understand.
I'll do something about it, so...
ですから…。
（カブト）イテッ。
Oww!
こんな時間に
何をしてるんだい！
もう寝る時間だよ！
What are you doing at this hour?!
You should be in bed!
この子は
まだ来たばかりですし→
院での時間割や
ルールを知りません。
He just got here and
doesn't know about
our curfews and rules!
大目に見てください。
Please give him another chance!
まったく…
マザーは甘いんだから。
You're too indulgent, Mother.
ほら　こっち来て
時計を見てみな。
Come here and
look at the clock!
今は　消灯時間
２０分も過ぎてる。
It's already 20 minutes
past lights-out time!
じゃあ　消灯時間は何時？
Which makes lights-out
what time?
今ここで
きっちり覚えましょうね。
Let's learn it right now!
ほら　何時だい？
ちゃんと自分で覚えるんだよ。
Well, what time is it?
You must learn it yourself!
この子は　まだ小さい。
He's still young.
計算どころか
時計が読めなくて当たり前だよ。
He doesn't know arithmetic
or how to tell time.
今日のところは　もう…。
（カブト）９時。
Let's just call it a night.
Nine o'clock.
正解です。
That's correct.
ハハ！
目が悪かっただけのようだね。
It seems it was just bad vision!
He's smart for his age!
この年で賢い。
早速　メガネがいるね。
We must get him glasses!
Huh? And where are we going
to get money for that?
はあ？　どこに
そんなお金があるんだい。
Goodness! If you can't see,
you should just speak up.
ったく　よく見えないなら
見えないと→
早く言えばいいのにね。
From now,
you'll be able to be on time.
これからは　時間を守れるわよね。
I just hope the lenses
are right for you.
ただ　レンズの度が
合ってるといいんだけど。
Thank... you...
(ありがとう…))
My name is symbolic.
（カブト）名は記号　メガネは道具。
My eyeglasses, a tool...
Thank you...
From the very beginning,
– I was a nobody...
– Thank you...
最初から
僕は何者でもなかった。
Thank you...
((ありがとう　ありがとう。
That's enough.
From the very beginning...
(もう十分よ))
I had...
最初から僕には…。
nothing.
何もない。
gozen reiji akari kieta machi
At midnight, in a city where the lights are out
koyoi wa odore tipsy night
I'm going to dance tonight Tipsy Night
tsukiakari mo todokanu basho ni wa
In a place where the moonlight doesn't reach
kodoku sae mo utau machi ga aru
There's a city that brings loneliness
kuruisou na furuesou na itami dake ga
There's only a maddening pain that makes me tremble
kowaresou na nakushisou na houseki da
It's like a fragile gemstone that could be easily lost
kuraberareru koto nado ubawareru koto nado nai
There's nothing to compare it to and it can't be stolen
kimi wa kimi de ii, saa waratte misete
You should just be yourself, Now show me a smile
nani mo kangaezutomo soko ni riyuu ga nakutomo
Even you don't think, Even if there is no reason
sore koso ga subarashii hajimari
This is a wonderful beginning
saa, yoake da
Now, dawn is about to break
gozen reiji akari kieta machi
At midnight, in a city where the lights are out
furikaereba sasou black night town
I look back and it beckons me Black Night Town
Mother... didn't know me. Why?
Why didn't she know me?
If she doesn't know me,
then who am I?
皆様　お変わりございませんか？
What were all those things
I received from Mother?
美空ひばりです。
My name, that I was one
of Mother's children,
では　最後まで
ごゆっくりお楽しみください。
even these glasses...
Who am I?
『木曜８時のコンサート
名曲！　にっぽんの歌』。
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Kabuto Yakushi"
It seems you no longer
see yourself clearly...
今回は　ご覧の豪華な歌手
１１組の皆さんによる→